

SKILLS

FRONT-END

JavaScript · TypeScript · React · C# ·

React Native · HTML · CSS

Back-End

NodeJS · Next JS

Database

MongoDB · Firebase

Tools and Libraries

Git · GitHub · ESLint · Jest · Axios ·

Tailwind CSS · Chakra UI · Ant Design ·

Sass

EDUCATION

Alpha JavaScript Track

Telerik Academy

01/2024 - 06/2024 Sofia, Bulgaria

Bachelor's degree, Accounting

VUZF

10/2009 - 07/2013 Sofia, Bulgaria

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian Native

English

Proficient

PASSIONS

- WEB DEVELOPMENT ENTHUSIAST
- ★ TAKING STROLLS IN NATURE
- BOARD GAMES WITH FRIENDS
- **COMPETITIVE GAMING**

RADOSLAV MARINOV

JavaScript Developer

- +359888788687 @ radoslav.marinov89@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Radoslav-Marinovv

SUMMARY

With 1+ year of experience in front-end development and five completed projects, I am a graduate of the Telerik Academy's Alpha JS track. I have developed strong skills in front-end technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and React, along with back-end knowledge in Node.js, Next.js, and Firebase. I am also well-versed in UI libraries such as Tailwind CSS, Ant Design, and Chakra UI.

I am eager to apply my diverse experience, creative thinking, and technical skills to contribute to the development of software projects and applications. Previously, I worked as a bartender and waiter in large hotels and restaurants (although not related to the job), where I not only gained valuable skills in teamwork, problem-solving, and interacting with diverse groups of people but also had the opportunity to teach and train others.

PROJECTS

Fitness Tracking Application: Motion Mate

Fitness tracking application, where users can track their daily exercises, such as calories burned, exercises done, or other activities. Users can set their goals and track their progress. They can also add their friends and see their progress as well.

- React.js, JavaScript, Firebase, Tailwind CSS
- daisy UI, Git

Forum: Tasty Recipe Talk

As part of a team, I was involved in creating the food recipe forum, creating the database connection, the GitHub repository. Building functionality and style of the project.

- · React.js, JavaScript, Firebase
- · Chakra UI, Git

Portfolio: Portfolio Hosted on Vercel

The portfolio is created with Next.js and a library called <u>Nextra(opens in a new tab)</u> that gives flexible generation of content based on MDX files.

- · Next.js, Type Script
- Nextra, MDX, Git

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer

02/2023 - 06/2023

Groshev & Partners

Sofia, Bulgaria

Took part in leading the communication with the client, planned the technologies that best met the client's requirements, and determined the necessary steps to meet the client's criteria.

- Next.js, React.js, Type Script, JSON
- Additional Libraries: TailwindCSS, Daisy UI, Google Blogger API
- Anttps://www.legalbg.net/

Front End Developer

06/2022 - 12/2022

TECHSTORM LTD

Sofia, Bulgaria

Participating in the creation of an MVP for a website as a front-end developer and a mobile application, extended existing functionality and implemented new features by completing assigned tasks.

- Tech stack: Next.js, React.js, React Native, Type Script, MongoDB, JSON.
- Additional Libraries: Auth0, Ant Design, Axios, Moment JS, TailwindCSS, React Router.